[Music]
want to become a homeowner in India
while living in the USA ICI Bank NRI
home loan can make your dream come true
choose from an exclusive database of
more than 50,000 pre-approved projects
Avail attractive interest rates and a
special processing fee get personalized
assistance and local support from ICICI
Bank offices in New York California and
Texas apply online and Avail Quick Loan
approval with digital sanction in only
five steps get a validity of 6 months on
your sanction letter from decision to
dispersement Avail NRI services in India
through Power of
Attorney you can Avail loan against
property topup and balance transfer
facilities with ICI Bank NRI Home Loan
in India your home in India is just a
click away with ICICI Bank and R home
loan